Safety 1st is committed to your right to privacy and will only use your data as set in our Privacy Policy below. Please read this information carefully. See a summary of our privacy practices below.

Click on the links to learn more and read the full policy below.

Effective date of this policy July 1, 2020

| **Collection and Sale of Data** |     |
| --- | --- |
| Do we sell your personal information | No  |
| Do we share or sell aggregate information | No  |
| Do we share your data with third party API partners | Yes, with consent |
| Do we use sensitive categories of data, like health information | Yes, with consent |
| Do we delete your data when you request account deletion | Yes |
| Do we retain your data for as long as we need it unless you request deletion | Yes |
|     |     |
| **Privacy Tools and Controls** |     |
| --- | --- |
| Can you control who sees your activity and content | Yes |
| Can you download and delete your data | No  |
|     |     |
| **Tracking** |     |
| --- | --- |
| Do we track your device location to provide services to you | Yes, for WiFi |
| Do we track your device location while you are not using the app | No  |
| Do we track your browsing activities on other sites | No  |
| Do we listen to you using your device microphone | No  |
|     |     |
| **Communication** |     |
| --- | --- |
| Do we give you advance notice when we make important changes to our Privacy Policy | Yes |
| Do we send you marketing communications | Opt-in Only |
| Do we send you push notifications | Yes |

PRIVACY POLICY
==============

This document sets forth the online Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy") of Safety 1st/Dorel Juvenile Group, Inc. ("DJG", “we”, or “us”) for the Safety 1st Baby Monitor mobile application, websites, content and features (collectively the "Services") and the Safety 1st Baby Monitor product (the “Product”). By using or accessing the Services and/or Product you signify your acknowledgment and assent to this Privacy Policy. If you have objections to the Privacy Policy, you should not access or use the Services and/or Product. This Privacy Policy does not govern privacy practices associated with offline activities or the collection of information other than through the Services and/or Product. This Privacy Policy is intended to help you understand how DJG and its affiliates collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide in connection to the Services and/or Product . It does not apply to the use or disclosure of information that is collected or obtained by DJG through other means. "Personal information" is defined as any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains.

By using our Services, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information by DJG as described in this Privacy Policy.

1. [PERSONAL INFORMATION](#01-personal-information)
2. [USAGE INFORMATION](#02-usage-information)
3. [POLICIES FOR CHILDREN](#03-policies-for-children)
4. [LINKED SITES](#04-linked-sites)
5. [OTHER DICSLOSURES](#05-other-disclosures)
6. [SECURITY](#06-security)
7. [DATA ACCESS, RETENTION AND DELETION](#07-dataaccess-retention-deletion)
8. [UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION AND PRIVACY PREFERENCES](#08-updating-personal-info)
9. [YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS](#09-california-privacy-rights)
10. [DATA TRANSFER](#10-data-transfer)
11. [PRIVACY ISSUES](#11-privacy-issues)
12. [PRIVACY-RELATED INQUIRIES AND COMPLAINTS](#12-privacy-inquiries-complaints)
13. [FORCE MAJEURE](#13-force-majeure)
14. [DISPUTE RESOLUTION](#14-dispute-resolution)
15. [EXPORT COMPLIANCE](#15-export-compliance)
16. [ELECTRONIC COMMUNICATIONS](#16-electronic-communications)
17. [CONTINUITY](#17-continuity)
18. [GENERAL](#18-general)
19. [CONTACT INFORMATION](#19-contact-information)

### 1\. PERSONAL INFORMATION

We collect personal information in connection with establishing and maintaining your account for the Services and responding to support inquiries, such as your first and last name, email address, location, internet cookies, mailing address, telephone number, and other personal information. Some of the information that we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data, you may not be able to engage in the particularly associated activity. Personal information collected in connection with the Services and/or Product will be used by DJG, its affiliates and Providers to perform and provide the Services and/or Product.

When you use the Services and/or Product, DJG or third parties authorized by DJG may also collect certain usage data and technical and routing information about your mobile device (collectively, “Usage Information”), such as browser type, operating system, device ID, CPU speed, and the Internet Protocol ("IP") address of your device. We use this Usage Information to facilitate and track your use of the Services and/or Product, to measure traffic patterns on the Services and/or Product and to otherwise administer our Services and/or Product. Without expressly informing you, we do not match such Usage Information with any of your personal information.

When you register your account, you may have opted-in to receive promotional communications, If you opted-in your personal information may be used by DJG and its affiliates to keep you informed about product upgrades, special offers, and other products and services of DJG, its affiliates and authorized third parties. If at any time you do not wish to receive promotional messages, you can use the opt-out method detailed in any message you receive or contact DJG customer service using the contact information below.

When you submit personal information to DJG through this Services and/or Product, you understand and agree that this information may be transferred across international boundaries and may be stored and processed in any of the countries in which DJG, its affiliates and subsidiaries maintain offices, including, without limitation, the United States of America and Canada.

DJG may use Providers to collect, store or access your personal information in connection with certain aspects of the Services and/or Product, however such Providers will be bound by contract not to use your personal information for their own purposes, to sell it or to disclose it to others unless necessary to ensure proper function of the Services and/or Product. Except as described in these Terms of Use, we don't rent, sell or otherwise distribute to others any personal information collected in connection with the Services and/or Product, including to any third party for such third party's direct marketing purposes. The Services and/or Product do not collect personally identifiable information about an individual user's online activities across third party web sites (and thus do not monitor any applicable Do Not Track indicator).

### 2\. USAGE INFORMATION

The Services and/or Product of DJG and its Providers automatically record certain information about how a person uses the Services and/or Product (“Usage Information”). Usage Information may include information such as a user’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, location, domain name, referring web page, device and browser type, operating system, device settings, the features of the Services and/or Product accessed and the time spent using those features, frequency with which the Services and/or Product are used by a user, search terms, the features and links on the Services and/or Product that a user clicked on or used, and other statistics. We use this information to administer and support the Services and/or Product and we analyze this information to improve and enhance the Services and tailor them to our users’ needs and preferences. We may use third party web analytics tools, including but not limited to Google® Analytics, Firebase, Kibana, and/or Crashlytics to collect and analyze Usage Information. Usage Information does not, in and of itself, identify you personally, but we may link it to personal information for account holders.

##### a. Services and/or Product Data

We may collect and record information relating to the setup, general performance, and operation of the Services and/or Product, including Services and/or Product status, User Content that a Services and/or Product’s sensors record (including audio, video, motion), and your Services and/or Product usage. We may store this data along with your personal information and other information about your use of the Services and/or Product. We use this information to allow you (and us) to monitor and operate the Services and/or Product

##### b. Location Data

The Services and/or Product may collect location information based on your IP address but do not collect precise GPS information about the location of your mobile device. We may associate this data with information associated with your account.

##### c. Cookies and Beacons

Usage Information may be collected via "cookies," which are small text files that are saved by your browser or device when you access the Services and/or Product. We (and our third-party providers, such as Google® Analytics) may use cookies to identify that you've logged in to the Services and/or Product and to tell us how and when you interact with the Services and/or Product. We may also use cookies to monitor aggregate usage and web traffic routing for the Services and/or Product and to customize and improve the Services and/or Product. Some apps and browsers have options to stop automatic acceptance of cookies or to prompt you before accepting cookies. You can also delete any cookie on your mobile device by uninstalling the mobile application. Please note, however, that if you don't permit cookies, you may not be able to access all portions or features of the Services and/or Product. Software technology called tags or web beacons (a.k.a. pixel tags or clear gifs) may also be employed to help us better manage Services and/or Product content and communications by informing us how certain content or features are used. These beacons (or other tracking technology) may be included in or associated with e-mails or other communications that you receive from us (or our Provider). We may link data gathered by web beacons or other tracking technology to the personal information of account holders.

##### d. Push Notifications

You may sign up to receive “push notification” messages. To make sure messages reach the correct devices, our third party provider relies on a device token unique to your mobile device. A device token is a unique identifier issued to the app by the operating system of your mobile device. While we may be able to access a list of the tokens, neither the App nor the tokens will reveal your identity, your unique device ID, or your contact information to us. The third party provider may collect the following: the time of an event, how a User came to our site, what search engine and search keywords users may have used to get to our site, information about the device our user is on such as their Operating System, and browser, as well as the city, region and country location of users. This location information enables DJG to send public health push notification messages that are relevant to certain geographic locations. If, at any time, you wish to stop receiving push notifications, simply adjust your phone settings or remove the App.

DJG and its affiliates may use aggregated or non-identifying data and Usage Information from the Services for analysis, technical, marketing or other business purposes and provide such aggregate or deidentified data to third parties for such purposes.

### 3\. POLICIES FOR CHILDREN

DJG does not knowingly collect or use any personal information from users under 18 years of age. No information should be submitted to the Services and/or Product by guests under 18 years of age, and guests under 18 years old are not permitted to provide Registration Information or to sign up for contests, newsletters, clubs or activities. The Services and/or Product are not offered or intended for use by, and DJG does not intend to collect personal information from, children under 18 years of age. Children under 18 years of age are directed not to use the Services and/or Product, whether to submit personal information or otherwise.

### 4\. LINKED SITES

The Services and/or Product contains links to other sites at which personal information is collected. In such instances, unless expressly provided to the contrary, the collection and use of your personal information will not be governed by this Privacy Policy but by the privacy policy applicable to that site. That privacy policy should identify the entity that is collecting your personal information.

DJG has established relationships with various service providers whose services may be available to you from this Services and/or Product or from websites that are linked to this Services and/or Product. Typically, these providers offer services that DJG customers might find useful, such as those that can be used in conjunction with DJG services and products. In order to use those services, you may be required to provide personal information to the providers. Unless expressly stated to the contrary, personal information that you provide while you are visiting a provider's website will not be subject to this Privacy Policy but to the privacy policy posted on such site. However, personal information that you provide while on this Services and/or Product in conjunction with a provider's service will be subject to this Privacy Policy. You should be aware that our agreements with these service providers often provide that they will share with DJG personal information collected from you. In such instances, DJG may use this information in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy.

### 5\. OTHER DICSLOSURES

We reserve the right to disclose without notice to you any information in our possession if we believe we are required to do so by law, to protect or defend DJG rights or property, or to respond to an emergency. Specific portions of the Services and/or Product may include additional or different provisions relating to collection and disclosure of personal information. In the event of a conflict between such provisions and this Privacy Policy, such specific terms shall control.

### 6\. SECURITY

While we use commercially reasonable efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information, we cannot guarantee that your data will always remain secure due to transmission errors, outside events, third party hacking or other causes, and we will not be liable therefor. See the section entitled "Confidentiality and Security" for additional terms and details.

### 7\. DATA ACCESS, RETENTION AND DELETION

You may review, update, correct or delete certain personal information or User Content associated with your account by logging into your account. If you wish to update or delete other personal information, you can contact us using the contact points specified below. We will take steps to modify or delete your personal information as soon as is practical, but some information may remain in archived/backup copies for our records or as otherwise required by law. Upon termination of your account, we will retain all personal information and User Content only as long as necessary to fulfill our obligations in connection with the Services and for any period of time necessary to comply with applicable law, including any applicable statute of limitation.

### 8\. UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION AND PRIVACY PREFERENCES

You have the right to access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences at any time. You may access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences (such as whether you wish to receive promotional communications from DJG or third parties) by calling 1-800-544-1108 (7 a.m. to 6 p.m. EST Monday through Thursday, and 7 a.m. to 4:30 p.m. EST on Fridays), faxing 1-800-207-8182, or writing to DJG using the contact point indicated below. Please include your name, address, and/or email address when you contact us. In your correspondence, please indicate with as much detail as possible the location on this Services and/or Product where you provided your personal information.

### 9\. YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

This section of our Privacy Policy pertains to consumers who reside in the State of California.

#### COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

This section describes the Personal Information we collect, and have collected, in the twelve months preceding the effective date of this Privacy Policy. We collect Personal Information from various sources and for various Business Purposes.

CATEGORIES OF PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED:

* Identifiers such as a real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, or other similar identifiers.
* Personal information, such as a credit card information
* Internet/network activity information collected through consumer interactions with our websites, advertisements, social media presences, and applications, including, but not limited to: System information such as IP address, browser type, browsing history, device type, operating system & version, geolocation data
* Commercial information, including records of service interactions, products purchase, obtained or considered, and product registrations
* Information from 3rd party suppliers, including commercial information necessary to complete purchase transactions and service requests on behalf of our retail partners
* Inferences drawn from the above information reflecting consumer preferences, behavior, predispositions and characteristics

We collect Personal Information from multiple sources and in multiple contexts, including:

* When a consumer opts-in to our marketing program by providing an email address on our website
* When a consumer initiates a purchase on our website
* When a consumer initiates a purchase through a Marketplace site where we sell product, including, but not limited to, Amazon 3P, Walmart Marketplace and Google Shopping
* When a consumer initiates a purchase of one or more of our products on a retailer website which, through existing arrangement with the retailer, is shipped and fulfilled directly by us
* When a consumer contacts our Consumer Care team directly
* When a consumer posts a product review for one of our products on a retailer website or on our website
* When a consumer interacts with, or creates an account on, our social media presence, applications or websites
* When a consumer completes the Product Registration process

#### DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

INFORMATION DISCLOSED FOR A BUSINESS PURPOSE

We have disclosed, within the preceding twelve months preceding the effective date of this Privacy Policy, and do disclose Personal Information to other business or third parties for various business purposes. These purposes include, but are not limited to, fulfillment of orders and shipments, execution of marketing and advertising activities, execution of service requests from consumers, and execution of product safety notices and recalls.

NO SALE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION:

As of the effective date of this Privacy Policy, We do not sell any consumer personal information to any third party. Any change in our position on the sale of consumer data will result in an update of this Privacy Policy and we will provide you with the opt-out and opt-in rights required by the CCPA.

**NON-DISCRIMNATION:**

We will not discriminate against any consumer for exercising their rights under the California Consumer Privacy Act

**YOUR RIGHTS AS A RESIDENT OF CALIFORNIA:**

If you are a resident of California, you have the right to request that we discloser to you the categories and specific pieces of information which we have collected about you in the preceding twelve months. We will honor such requests to the extent required by applicable law. As a resident of California, there are three categories of request which we support:

1. 'Data Subject Access Requests': you have the right to request that we disclose to you the categories of information and specific pieces of information which we have collected about you in the twelve months preceding your request, including the sources from which we have collected data, the third parties with whom we have shared personal information, and the business purposes for the collection and, to the extent applicable, sharing of information with third parties.
2. Deletion of Personal Information ('Right to be Forgotten'): to the extent applicable by law, you have the right to request that we delete personal information about you that we have collected from you. Exceptions include where personal information is maintained for:

* Transaction completion;
* Detection of security incidents or protection against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity;
* Debugging for identification and repair of functionality errors;
* Exercise of free speech;
* Compliance with the California Electronic Communications Privacy Act;
* Engaging in scientific, historical or statistical research in the public interest;
* Internal uses reasonably aligned with consumer expectations;
* Compliance with a legal obligation; or
* Otherwise lawful use, compatible with the context in which the consumer provided the information.

4. Data Portability Request: you have the right to obtain your personal information in a format that allows you to transmit it to another organization. We will deliver personal information as required by law within 45 days after receipt of a verifiable request, unless we notify you, as required by law, that we require additional time to respond.

In all three cases, above, we will first, as required by law, verify the request.

**HOW TO MAKE A REQUEST:**

You may make a request to exercise the above rights by contacting our Consumer Care group by contact us through the means listed below.

### 10\. DATA TRANSFER

You understand and agree that personal information provided in connection with the Services and/or Product may be transferred across national boundaries and may be stored and processed in any of the countries in which DJG or its Providers maintain facilities, including, without limitation, the United States of America and Canada, and you consent to the transfer of your personal information to such jurisdictions. In the event DJG or its assets are sold, merged or otherwise involved in a corporate transaction, DJG may transfer affected customer and personal information without your consent.

### 11\. PRIVACY ISSUES

If you have questions concerning a privacy issue or wish to update, correct or modify your personal information or privacy preferences (such as to indicate you do not wish to receive promotional communications), you may contact DJG customer service using the contact information below.

### 12\. PRIVACY-RELATED INQUIRIES AND COMPLAINTS

If you believe that DJG has not complied with this online Privacy Policy with respect to your personal information or you have other related inquiries or concerns, you may write to DJG at the contact address indicated below. In your letter, please describe in as much detail as possible the nature of your inquiry or the ways in which you believe that the DJG online Privacy Policy has not been followed. We will attempt to investigate your inquiry or complaint promptly. Please note that if you provide DJG with inconsistent privacy preferences (for example, by indicating on one occasion that third parties may contact you with marketing offers and indicating on another occasion that they may not), DJG cannot guarantee that your most recent privacy preference will be honored. Also, please note that DJG is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of non-DJG websites to which this Site or any other DJG website may link. You should review the privacy policy of such sites before using the sites.

### 13\. FORCE MAJEURE

DJG and its Providers shall not be responsible for delays or failures in performance resulting from acts or circumstances beyond their control, including without limitation acts of God, strikes or other labor disputes, riots, acts of war, malfunction of portions of the Internet or another third party network, governmental regulations promulgated after the effective date of these Terms of Use, communication line, power or equipment failures, fires or other disasters, and acts of third parties, including hackers (each a "Force Majeure Event").

### 14\. DISPUTE RESOLUTION

PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING SECTION CAREFULLY BECAUSE IT REQUIRES YOU TO ARBITRATE DISPUTES AND IT LIMITS THE MANNER IN WHICH YOU CAN SEEK RELIEF. To the fullest extent permitted by law, these Terms of Use, and any claim, dispute, action, cause of action, issue, or request for relief relating to these Terms or Use, the Services or Product, will be governed by the laws of Indiana, U.S.A., without giving effect to any conflicts of laws principles that require the application of the laws of a different jurisdiction. To the fullest extent permitted by law, any dispute or claim relating to this Privacy Policy, the Services and/or Product will be resolved by binding arbitration under the Commercial Arbitration Rules of the American Arbitration Association ("AAA"), rather than in court (except that you may assert claims in small claims court if your claims qualify, and you or we may seek injunctive or equitable relief in court to stop infringement or other misuse of intellectual property rights). The Federal Arbitration Act and federal arbitration law apply to the enforcement of this agreement to arbitrate. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW WE EACH AGREE THAT ANY DISPUTE RESOLUTION PROCEEDINGS WILL BE CONDUCTED ONLY ON AN INDIVIDUAL BASIS AND NOT IN A CLASS, CONSOLIDATED OR REPRESENTATIVE ACTION. This arbitration provision does not preclude you from bringing issues to the attention of federal, state, or local agencies. Such agencies can, if the law allows, seek relief against us on your behalf. If for any reason a claim proceeds in court (other than small claims court) rather than in arbitration you and DJG each waive any right to a jury trial and irrevocably consent to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts located in Columbus, Indiana in connection with any such action. You and DJG waive any objection based on lack of personal jurisdiction, place of residence, improper venue or forum non conveniens in any such action.

### 15\. EXPORT COMPLIANCE

Although the Services and/or Product may be accessible worldwide, our Services and/or Product are not designed for use in all countries, and some or all of the features of the Services and/or Product may not work or be appropriate for use in a particular country. The Services and/or Product and related technology are subject to U.S. export control laws and may be subject to export or import regulations in other countries. You represent and warrant that you are not named on any U.S. government list of restricted or prohibited persons or entities or located in a country that is subject to U.S. government embargo or restrictions. You agree to comply with the export laws and regulations of the United States and other applicable jurisdictions in providing and using the Services and/or Product. You will not permit anyone to access or use the Services and/or Product in violation of any U.S. export embargo, prohibition or restriction.

### 16\. ELECTRONIC COMMUNICATIONS

When you use the Services and/or Product, send us e-mails, or send text messages, you are communicating with us electronically, and you consent to receive communications from us electronically. We may communicate with you by e-mail, text message, or by transmitting notices via the App. You agree that all agreements, notices, disclosures and other communications that we provide to you electronically satisfy any legal requirement that such communications be in writing.

### 17\. CONTINUITY

Please note that if DJG sells assets (or the assets of a division or subsidiary) to another entity, or DJG (or a division or subsidiary) is acquired by, or merged with, another entity, DJG may provide to such entity customer and personal information that is related to that part of our business that was sold to or merged with the other entity without your consent.

Specific elements of the Services and/or Product may include additional or different provisions relating to collection and disclosure of personal information. In the event of a conflict between such provisions and this Privacy Policy, such specific terms shall control.

### 18\. GENERAL

These Terms of Use, including any applicable Service Terms and other materials incorporated herein, represent the entire agreement and understanding relating to the use of the Services and prevail over any prior or contemporaneous, conflicting or additional communications. The English version of this Privacy Policy shall govern over any translation. You acknowledge and agree that each of DJG’s Providers, as well as Apple, Google and other applicable OS providers, shall be considered a third party beneficiary of these Terms of Use and shall have the right to enforce this Privacy Policy directly against you in connection with any dispute or breach.

Any unauthorized access, modification or change of any information, or any interference with the availability of or access to the Services is strictly prohibited. DJG reserves all legal rights and remedies available to it and this Privacy Policy shall in no way be deemed a limitation or waiver of any other rights DJG may have.

Our failure to assert a right or insist upon compliance with any term or condition shall not constitute a waiver of that right or excuse any subsequent noncompliance. If any provision of this Privacy Policy is deemed unlawful, void or for any reason unenforceable, then that provision shall be deemed severable from the remaining terms and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining provisions. The parties agree that any invalid provision shall be deemed to be restated so as to be enforceable to the maximum extent permissible under law consistent with the original intent and economic terms of the invalid provision.

### 19\. CONTACT INFORMATION

Dorel Juvenile Group, Inc. Consumer Relations Department  
P.O. Box 2609, Columbus, IN 47202-2609  
  
Email: [consumer@djgusa.com](mailto:consumer@djgusa.com)  
Phone: 1 (800) 544-1108  
Text: 1 (812) 203-4747  
Fax: 1 (800) 207-8182  
Available 7 a.m. to 6 p.m. ET Monday through Thursday, and 7 a.m. to 4:30 p.m. ET on Fridays.
